(Howard:)Boy, some of the physical comedy
with Jar Jar
(Howard:)is a little tough to watch.
(Leonard:)At least they toned him down
in the second one.
(Penny:)Yeah, he is pretty stupid.
(Raj:)Hey, we can say it. You can't.
(Penny:)-Hey, guys.
-Happy Star Wars Day!
A Death Star cake!
(Amy:)Yeah, we were hoping
it might cheer you up.
(Bernadette:)And even though it meant
we had to miss the movies,
(Bernadette:)we could still be
part of the fun.
(Howard:)Well, you didn't miss anything.
We just started over.
(Bernadette:)Son of a bitch.
I (ORCHESTRAL SCORE)
(Sheldon:)You're back.
(Arthur:)Yeah, apparently...
(Arthur:)...I'm here whenever...
whenever you need me.
(Sheldon:)That's nice.
(Arthur:)Maybe for you.
(Sheldon:)Why do I need you now?
(Arthur:)Well, as near as I could tell,
(Arthur:)you fell asleep watching Star Wars,
and now you're dreaming
you're watching Star Wars.
(Sheldon:)So?
I mean, don't you see
a problem there?
I mean, how you're spending
your limited time on earth?
(Sheldon:)Not at all.
OK, good luck to you.